content for children eh what is the girl
contenido para niños eh que es la chica
saying I lied to you I don't have Netflix and him
diciendo te mentí no tengo Netflix y él
saying Oh no holding his hand but on
diciendo Oh no agarrandole la mano pero
top of that the title implies something
es que encima el título implica algo
even worse alone at home with my sister
todavía peor solo en casa con mi hermana
roblox youtubers who are supposed to
youtubers de roblox que supone que
generate children's content making the
generan contenido infantil haciendo el
content as 18 as possible alone at
contenido lo más más 18 posible solo en
home with my sister I lied to you I don't have
casa con mi hermana te mentí no tengo
Netflix trying to make cyber cheese
Netflix que intenta hacer ciber queso
with me and goes and writes me this is real
conmigo y va y me escribe esto es real
eh And he writes me hello and some of you will say Oh
eh Y me escribe hola y algunos diréis Ay
Dalas but he only wrote you Hello I
Dalas pero solo te escribió Hola no
wasn't trying to flirt with you anymore
estaba intentando ligar contigo ya
Tell me another joke shut up shut up I
Cuéntame otro chiste cállate cállate me
thought there would be more conversations from
creía que habría más conversaciones de
Lola El Dallas has understood cyber cheese
Lola El Dallas ha entendido ciber queso
well the obs was open and was
bueno el obs estaba abierto y estaba
recording Yes I know and why did you do it
grabando Sí lo sé y por qué lo hiciste
but I didn't record I mean I deleted it he sent him
pero no grabé o sea lo eliminé le mandó
a photo without realizing that he was
una foto sin darse cuenta de que estaba
recording that day He's already saying I
grabando ese día Ya está diciendo lo
recorded it but I deleted it I just wanted to get
grabé pero lo eliminé solo quería llamar
your attention to see if you noticed
tu atención para ver si te dasas cuenta
and really watched the video and why did you
y realmente vías el video y por qué
want to record me I only recorded you to
Querías grabarme te grabé solamente para
see if you noticed
ver si te dabas cuenta